A Finding Aid to the Esther McCoy Papers, circa 1876-1990, bulk 1938-1989, in the Archives of American Art AAA.mccoesth
Archives of American Art
- Photographs and Slides, circa 1876-1989; Series 9; (Boxes 31-38, 41-46, 51; 8.7 linear feet)
  - Architects, circa 1898-1980s; 9.2
    - Davidson, J. R. (Box 33)
      - Mrs. Paul Kingsley House (1946), 1948; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 33, Folder 71)
      - Davidson House and Studio (1947), circa 1940s; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 33, Folder 72)
      - Osherenko House (1949), circa 1950s; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 33, Folder 73)
      - Rachford Harris House (1950), circa 1950s; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Dann House (1952), circa 1950s; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Rabinowitz House (1957), circa 1957; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Jokl House (1958), circa 1958; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - "House of the Book,", 1959; (Oversized Items housed in Box 43) (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Various Projects, 1926-1931, 1940-1957; (Photographs by Julius Shulman and Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 6-7)
      - Unidentified projects, circa 1940s-1950s; (Photographs by Julius Shulman and Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - De la Lama, Victor, House, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Del Moral, Enrique, Del Moral House, circa 1952 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Eggers, Henry, Unidentified House, circa 1950s (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Ellwood, Craig, Scientific Data Systems Building (1966-1969), circa 1960s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Ellwood, Craig, Various Projects, circa 1960s (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Fletcher, Charles, Lummis House, circa 1950s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Franzen, Ulrich and Associates, Various Projects, circa 1967-1968 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Fuller, R. Buckminster, Dome, 1967 World Exhibition, circa 1967 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Gehry, Frank O., Various Projects, circa 1970s (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Gill, Irving (Box 34)
    - Photographs of Irving Gill, circa 1910-1912; (2 folders) (Box 34, Folder 18-19)
      - McKenzie House (1898), circa 1898 (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - Stephens house (1898), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - Birckhead House (1901-1902), circa mid-1900s (Box 34, Folder 22)
      - Ellen Mason House (1901-1902), circa early-1900s (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - Louis B. McCagg House (1901-1902), circa early 1900s (Box 34, Folder 24)
      - "Wildacre" Olmstead House (1901-1902), circa mid-1900s (Box 34, Folder 25)
      - Christian Science Church, San Diego (1904), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 26)
      - George Marston House (1904), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 27)
      - Douglas House (1905), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 28)
      - Burnham House (1906), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 29)
      - Lee Residence, No. 1 (1906), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 30)
      - Bailey House (1907), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 31)
      - Melville Klauber House (1907), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 32)
      - Laughlin House (1907), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 33)
      - 3928 3rd Avenue (circa 1908), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 34)
      - Blair House (1908), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 35)
      - Darst Flats (1908), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 36)
      - Scripps Institution of Oceanography (1908), circa mid-1900s (Box 34, Folder 37)
      - St. James Chapel (1908), circa mid-1900s (Box 34, Folder 38)
      - Wilson Acton Hotel (1908), circa mid-1900s (Box 34, Folder 39)
      - Bishop's School (1909-1916), circa 1910s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 40-41)
      - Fountain, San Diego (1909), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 42)
      - Miltimore House (1911), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 43)
      - Riverside Portland Cement Co. (1911), circa mid-1900s (Box 34, Folder 44)
      - Thompson House (1912), circa mid-1900s; (Oversized items housed in Box 43; photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 45)
      - Pacific Electric Railway Station (1913), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 46)
      - Women's Club (1913), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 47-48)
      - Community House and Playground, La Jolla (1914), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 49)
      - Dodge House (1916), circa 1950s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 50-52)
      - Dodge House, Demolition Photographs, 1970; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 53)
      - Dodge House, Julius Shulman Photographs, circa 1950s (Box 34, Folder 54)
      - Dodge House, Duplicate Photographs, circa 1950s (Box 34, Folder 55-56)
      - Ellen Scripps House (1916), circa 1950s; (Oversized items housed in Box 43) (Box 34, Folder 57)
      - Horatio West Court (1919), circa 1950s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 58)
      - Christian Science Church, Coronado (1929), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 59)
      - City Hall, Oceanside (1929), circa 1930-1950s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 60)
      - Fire House and Police Station, Oceanside (1929), circa 1930-1950s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 61)
      - Navada Street School (1931), circa 1930s-1950s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 62)
      - Rancho Barona Chapel (1933), circa 1930s-1950s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 63)
      - 7th Street House, undated (Box 34, Folder 64)
      - Various Projects, circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 65-69)
      - Mounted Photographs of Various Projects, circa 1950s (Box 34, Folder 70-71)
    - Goldfinger, Myron Henry, House on Long Beach Island, NJ, circa 1960s; (Oversized items housed in Box 43) (Box 34, Folder 72)
    - Goodhue, Bertram, Balboa Park Buildings (1914), 1903-circa 1950s (Box 34, Folder 73)
    - Goodhue, Bertram, Los Angeles Public Library (1925), circa 1950s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 34, Folder 74)
    - Grace, Harrison, Grace Bros. Farm, Texarkana, circa 1950s (Box 34, Folder 75)
    - Greene, Charles and Henry (Box 35)
      - Photographs of Charles and Henry Greene, 1953 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Irwin House (1906), 1968 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - R. R. Blacker House (1907), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - D. B. Gamble House (1908), circa 1959; (Photographs by Julius Shulman and Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Crowe House (1913), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Various Projects, circa 1959 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Gregotti, Vittorio, Industrial Building, circa 1960s (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Gregotti, Vittorio, La Rinascente Department Store, circa 1960s (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Jones, A. Quincy, UCLA, University Research Library (1964), circa 1964; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Jones, A. Quincy, Various Projects, circa 1956; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Harris, Harwell Hamilton (Box 35)
      - Fellowship Park House (1935), circa 1930s (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Havens House (1940), circa 1940 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Various Projects, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 35, Folder 13-15)
    - Kahn, Louis, Salk Institute (1965), circa 1965; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Koenig, Pierre, Photographs of Pierre Koenig, circa 1957 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Koenig, Pierre, Various Projects, circa 1960s (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Lautner, John, Photographs of John Lautner, undated (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Lautner, John, Various Projects, circa 1950s-1960s; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Le Corbusier, Visual Arts Center, Harvard University, circa 1961 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Lopez-Bermudez, "$1500 House,", circa 1952 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Lustig, Alvin, Accessory Shop, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Madaleno, Juan Sordo, Various Projects, circa 1950s (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Maiden, Rowan, Nepenthe Restaurant, circa 1950 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Mariscal, Nicolas, House, undated (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Martinez, Ramon Torres, House, circa 1950s (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Maybeck, Bernard (Box 35)
      - Photographs of Bernard Maybeck, circa 1940 (Box 35, Folder 28)
      - Hearst Hall (1899), circa mid-1900s (Box 35, Folder 29)
      - Wyntoon on McCloud River (1902), circa mid-1900s (Box 35, Folder 30)
      - Unitarian Church, Paolo Alto (1906), circa mid-1900s (Box 35, Folder 31)
      - Lawson House (1907), circa 1950s (Box 35, Folder 32)
      - First Church of Christ Scientists (1910-1912), circa 1950s; (Oversized items housed in Box 43; photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 35, Folder 33-34)
      - Chick House (1913), circa 1913 (Box 35, Folder 35)
      - Palace of Fine Arts (1913-1915), undated (Box 35, Folder 36)
      - Marx Greene House (1916), 1959 (Box 35, Folder 37)
      - Bingham House (1917), circa mid-1900s (Box 35, Folder 38)
      - Packard Agencies (1926-1929), circa mid-1900s (Box 35, Folder 39)
      - Earle C. Anthony House (1927), circa mid-1900s (Box 35, Folder 40)
      - Various Projects, circa 1910-1950s; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 35, Folder 41-43)
    - McCue and Associates, Chevron Research Laboratory, circa 1965 (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - Mies van der Rohe, Ludwig (Box 35)
      - Photographs of Ludwig Mies van der Rohe, circa 1960 (Box 35, Folder 45)
      - Museum of Fine Arts Houston (1958), circa 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 46)
      - Seagram Building (1958), circa 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 47)
      - Ron Bacardi Administration Building (1961), circa 1961 (Box 35, Folder 48)
      - Redevelopment Project, circa 1960 (Box 35, Folder 49)
      - Unidentified Administration Building, circa 1960 (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - Miller, Leroy R., House, undated (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - Morgan, William, Various Projects, 1966-1968; (Oversized items housed in Box 43) (Box 35, Folder 52)
    - Morrison, Manuel Rosen, Various Projects, circa 1960s (Box 35, Folder 53)
    - Nervi, Pier, Various Projects, circa 1960s (Box 35, Folder 54-55)
    - Neutra, Richard (Box 35)
      - Lovell House (1929), circa mid-1900s (Box 35, Folder 56)
      - Lovell House, Julius Shulman Photographs, circa mid-1900s (Box 35, Folder 57)
      - Lovell House, Negatives, circa mid-1900s (Box 35, Folder 58)
      - Bailey House (1946), circa 1940s (Box 35, Folder 59)
      - Tramaine House (1948), circa 1948; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 35, Folder 60)
      - Various Projects, circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 35, Folder 61)
    - O'Gorman, Juan (Box 35)
      - Photographs of Juan O'Gorman, circa 1950s-1960s; (Oversized items housed in Box 43) (Box 35, Folder 62)
      - O'Gorman House (1951), circa 1951; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 35, Folder 63-67)
      - Central Library, University of Mexico (1952), circa 1952; (Oversized items housed in Box 43; photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 35, Folder 68-69)
      - Chapultepec Castle (1960-1961) (Transparencies), circa 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Primary School, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Taxco Mural, circa 1956; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Communications Building, University of Mexico, circa 1950s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Various Projects, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Otto, Frei, German Pavilion at Expo 67, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Palladio, Andrea, Various Projects, circa 1960s; (Oversized items housed in Box 43) (Box 36, Folder 7-8)
    - Pani, Mario, Various Projects, circa 1947-1950s (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Pelli, Cesar (Box 36)
      - Photographs of Cesar Pelli, circa 1980s (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - San Bernardino City Hall (1972), circa 1972 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - International Jewelry Centre, circa 1965; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Various Projects, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Pereira and Luckman, IBM Tower, circa 1956-1959; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Pereira and Luckman, John Jay Hopkins Laboratory, 1958; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Piano, Renzo and Richard Rogers, Various Projects, circa 1970s (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Platt, Anthony C., Penn State Project, undated (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Polshek, James, Research Laboratory in Japan, circa 1964 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Polshek, James, Various Projects, circa 1960s (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Ponti, Gio, Various Projects, circa 1957-1962 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Rapson, Ralph, Tyrone Guthrie Theatre, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Reid, Merritt and James Watson Reid, Hotel del Coronado (1887), circa mid-1900s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Revell, Viljo, Apartment House, Helsinki (1962), circa 1962 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Ricci, Leonardo, "Birth of a Village in an Underdeveloped Area,", 1966 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Ricci, Leonardo, Various Projects, circa 1963-1967 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Roehrig, Frederick, Hotel Green (1903), circa 1960s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Safdie, Moshe, Habitat 67, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Sant'Elia, Antonio, Various Projects, circa 1960s (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Sartoris, Alberto, Various Projects, circa 1960s (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Schindler, R. M. (Box 36)
      - Hampden Club (1916-1917), circa 1916-1917 (Box 36, Folder 30)
      - Kings Road House (1921-1922), circa 1920s-1953; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 31)
      - Lowes House (1923), circa 1950s; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 32)
      - Pueblo Ribera Court (1923), circa 1923-1925 (Box 36, Folder 33)
      - Gibling House (1926), circa 1926-1927 (Box 36, Folder 34)
      - Lovell Beach House (1925-1926), circa 1926; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 35)
      - Wolfe House (1928), circa 1928, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 36)
      - Gisela Bernati Cabin (1937), circa 1937 (Box 36, Folder 37)
      - Rodakiewicz House (1937), circa 1937; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 38-39)
      - Daugherty House (Sugarbush Hill) (1945), circa 1945; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 40)
      - Kallis House (1946), circa 1946 (Box 36, Folder 41)
      - Erlik House (1950), circa 1950; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 42)
      - Various Projects, circa 1915-1950s (Box 36, Folder 43-45)
    - Sedletsky, Marcel, Various Projects, circa 1965-1966 (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - Soriano, Raphael (Box 36)
      - Photographs of Raphael Soriano, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 36, Folder 47)
      - Jewish Community Center (1939), circa 1939; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 48)
      - Lukens House and Studio (1940), circa 1940; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 49)
      - Colby Apartments (1952), circa 1952; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 50)
      - Eichler House (1955), circa 1955 (Box 36, Folder 51)
      - Adolph's Office Building and Research Laboratory (1958), circa 1958; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 52)
      - McCauley House (1959), circa 1959 (Box 36, Folder 53)
      - Cooke House (1961), circa 1961 (Box 36, Folder 54)
      - San Francisco Tower (1969), circa 1969 (Box 36, Folder 55)
      - Various Projects, circa 1930s-1960s; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 56-57)
    - Spaulding, Sumner and John Rex, Eckberg House, circa 1950s; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 58)
    - Tigerman, Stanley, Instant City Project, circa 1965 (Box 36, Folder 59)
    - Wong, Worley K. and John Campbell, Various Projects, circa 1950s (Box 36, Folder 60)
    - Wright, Frank Lloyd, Various Projects, circa 1920-1950s; (Photographs by Julius Shulman and Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 61)
    - Wright, Lloyd, Various Projects, circa 1920s-1960s (Box 36, Folder 62)
    - Wyman, George, Bradbury Building (1893), circa 1950s; (Photographs by Julius Shulman and Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 63-64)
    - Miscellaneous Architects, A-Z (Includes portraits of architects), circa 1950s-1980s; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 65-66)
    - Unidentified Architect, Church, undated (Box 36, Folder 67)
    - Unidentified Architect, Supermarket, San Olona Vittore, Italy, undated (Box 36, Folder 68)
    - Unidentified Photographs of Architects and Architecture, circa 1950s-1970s; (Oversized rolled items housed in RD 51) (Box 36, Folder 69)
    - Oversized Photographs of Barragan House by Luis Barragan, circa 1948; (Scanned with Box 33, Folder 35) (Box 42)
    - Oversized Photographs of Jardines del Pedregal (includes Alfred Ortega House)by Luis Barragan, circa 1940s-1950s; (Scanned with Box 33, Folder 36) (Box 42)
    - Oversized Photographs of Prieto Lopez House by Luis Barragan, undated; (Scanned with Box 33, Folder 37) (Box 42)
    - Oversized Photographs of Pfeifferling House by J. R. Davidson, circa 1919; (Scanned with Box 33, Folders 57-58) (Box 43)
    - Oversized Photographs of Hotel Shoreland by J. R. Davidson, circa 1937; (Scanned with Box 33, Folder 60) (Box 43)
    - Oversized Photographs of "House of the Book" by J. R. Davidson, 1959; (Scanned with Box 34, Folder 5) (Box 43)
    - Oversized Photographs of Thompson House by Irving Gill, circa mid-1900s; (Scanned with Box 34, Folder 45) (Box 43)
    - Oversized Photographs of Ellen Scripps House by Irving Gill, circa 1950s; (Scanned with Box 34, Folder 57) (Box 43)
    - Oversized Photographs of House on Long Beach Island, NJ, by Myron Goldfinger, circa 1960s; (Scanned with Box 34, Folder 72) (Box 43)
    - Oversized Photographs of First Church of Christ Scientists by Bernard Maybeck, circa 1950s; (Scanned with Box 35, Folders 33-34) (Box 43)
    - Oversized Photographs of Various Projects by William Morgan, circa 1966-1968; (Scanned with Box 35, Folder 52) (Box 43)
    - Oversized Photographs of Juan O'Gorman, circa 1950s-1960s; (Scanned with Box 35, Folder 62) (Box 43)
    - Oversized Photographs of Central Library, University of Mexico by Juan O'Gorman, circa 1952; (Scanned with Box 35, Folders 68-69) (Box 43)
    - Oversized Photographs of Various Projects by Andrea Palladio, circa 1960s; (Scanned with Box 36, Folders 7-8) (Box 43)
    - Oversized Unidentified Photographs of Architecture, undated; (See also Box 36, Folder 69; not scanned) (Box RD 51)
  - Case Study Houses, circa 1945-1962; 9.3
    Found here are photographs of architecture designed for the Case Study House program. McCoy researched and wrote about this program extensively, and researchers should note that additional photographs of these houses can be found within her writing files in Series 4 for both her book, Modern California Houses: Case Study Houses 1946-1962, and the exhibition catalog, Blueprints for Modern Living: History and Legacy of the Case Study House. Some of these files also include a photograph of the architect(s). Most of the photographs were taken by Esther McCoy, Julius Shulman, Marvin Rand, or the architect.
    Portions of this subseries have been scanned. Photographs taken by Julius Shulman and Marvin Rand have not been scanned and are noted in the folder heading.
    Photographs are arranged alphabetically by architect and then by project number.
    - Abell, Thornton, Case Study House #7, circa 1950s (Box 36, Folder 70)
    - Buff, Straub and Hensman, Case Study House #20, circa 1957-1958; (Photographs by Julius Shulman and Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 71)
    - Davidson, J. R., Case Study Houses #1, #11, #15, circa 1945-1947; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 36, Folder 72)
    - Eames, Charles, Case Study House #8, circa 1949; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Eames, Charles and Eero Saarinen, Case Study House #9, circa 1949; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Ellwood, Craig, Case Study House#16, circa 1952-1953; (Photographs by Julius Shulman and Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Ellwood, Craig, Case Study House #17, circa 1957 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Ellwood, Craig, Case Study House #18, circa 1956-1958; (Photographs by Marvin Rand have not been scanned) (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Jones and Emmons, Case Study House #24, circa 1961 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Killingsworth, Brady, and Smith, Case Study House #23, circa 1959-1960; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Killingsworth, Brady, and Smith, Case Study Hosue #25, circa 1962; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Knorr, Don, Case Study House #19, circa 1957 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Koenig, Pierre, Case Study House #21, circa 1958-1960; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Koenig, Pierre, Case Study House #22, circa 1959-1960; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 37, Folder 11-12)
    - Neutra, Richard, Case Study Houses #6, #13, circa 1945-1946; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Neutra, Richard, Case Study House #20, circa 1947-1948; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Nomland, Kemper and Kemper Jr., Case Study House #10, circa 1945-1947; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Smith, R. Whitney, Case Study Houses #5, #12, circa 1945-1946; (Photographs by Julius Shulman have not been scanned) (Box 37, Folder 16)